Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm As-Broadcast Scripts, 1928-1958 RL.00655
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Kraft Cheese, 1929-1958; 25
  - Kraft Television Theatre, 1947-1958; 44
    - The Devil as a Roaring Lion, 1956 Jan. 18 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Diamond As Big As the Ritz, 1955 Sept. 28 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Discoverers, 1957 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Divine Drudge, 1952 Oct. 29 (Film-reel 908)
    - The Duel, 1957 Mar. 6 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Emperor Jones, 1955 Feb. 23 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Empty House, 1952 Dec. 3 (Film-reel 908)
    - The Failure, 1955 Aug. 17 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Fool Killer, 1956 Mar. 7 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Gentle Grafter, 1956 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Girl Who Saw Too Much, 1956 Aug. 29 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Glass Wall, 1957 May 15 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Grapefruits to Lisbon, 1956 Oct. 24 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Grass Harp, 1952 Sept. 17 (Film-reel 907)
    - The Great Big Doorstep, 1952 July 16 (Film-reel 907)
    - The Guest Room, 1952 Dec. 17 (Film-reel 908)
    - The Inn, 1952 May 14 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Just and the Unjust, 1956 Dec. 26 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The King's Bounty, 1955 Sept. 21 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Last Mile, 1952 Apr. 9 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Life of Mickey Mantle, 1956 Oct. 3 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Long Arm, 1956 July 11 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Lost Shadow, 1956 Apr. 11 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Lost Weekend, 1956 Mar. 21 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Man in Half Moon Street, 1952 Apr. 30 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Man on Roller Skates, 1956 Feb. 15 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Man on Roller Skates, 1956 Feb. 15 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Man Who Couldn't Say No, 1957 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Medallion, 1957 Apr. 3 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Million Dollar Rookie, 1955 May 25 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Mob, 1955 June 29 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Mollusk, 1952 Feb. 20 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Music Master, 1952 July 30 (Film-reel 907)
    - The New Gossoon, 1952 Jan. 2 (Film-reel 905)
    - The New Tenant, 1952 Oct. 8 (Film-reel 907)
    - The New Tenant, 1952 Oct. 8 (Film-reel 908)
    - The Night of May Third, 1956 June 6 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Night Watchers, 1955 Mar. 9 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Ninth Hour, 1956 Dec. 5 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Peaceful Warrior, 1952 Jan. 23 (Film-reel 905)
    - The Plunge, 1956 Sept. 26 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Roaring 20th, 1957 June 5 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Round Table, 1952 Jan. 16 (Film-reel 905)
    - The Rugged Path, 1952 Mar. 26 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Ryan Girl, 1952 Apr. 2 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Sea is Boiling Hot, 1958 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 1008)
    - The Sears Girls, 1956 Jan. 11 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Singin' Idol, 1957 Jan. 30 (Film-reel 1002)
    - The Skin Game, 1952 Feb. 13 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Skin Game, 1955 Feb. 2 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Small Hours, 1952 Aug. 27 (Film-reel 907)
    - The Spell of the Tigress, 1958 Feb. 5 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Story of Mary Surratt, 1955 Mar. 23 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Straw, 1955 July 13 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Summit, 1952 Apr. 23 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Thief, 1952 Mar. 12 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Thieving Magpies, 1956 Jan. 4 (Film-reel 1003)
    - The Third Visitor, 1952 May 28 (Film-reel 906)
    - The Third Visitor, 1952 May 28 (Film-reel 907)
    - The Velvet Trap, 1958 Jan. 8 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Woman at High Hollow, 1958 Feb. 26 (Film-reel 1007)
    - The Wonderful Gift (missing), 1956 Dec. 19 (Film-reel 1004)
    - The Written Word, 1955 Jan. 19 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Ticket and the Tempest, 1955 Nov. 9 (Film-reel 1001)
    - Time for Turning, 1952 July 2 (Film-reel 907)
    - Time Lock (missing), 1956 Nov. 28 (Film-reel 1004)
    - Treatment for a Long Flight, undated (Film-reel 1011)
    - Trucks Welcome, 1955 Oct. 12 (Film-reel 1003)
    - Two Times Two, 1955 Aug. 10 (Film-reel 1003)
    - What Anne Brought Home, 1952 Mar. 5 (Film-reel 906)
    - Whim of Iron, 1955 Apr. 6 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Woman of Principle, 1955 Sept. 7 (Film-reel 1003)
    - 1947 June 25-Nov. 12 (Film-reel 364)
      Through second act of Nov. 12, Ladies in Retirement
    - 1947 Nov. 12-Dec. (Film-reel 365)
      From third act of Nov. 12, Ladies in Retirement
    - 1948 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 424)
    - 1948 Apr.-Aug. (Film-reel 425)
      No broadcasts June 23, July 14 due to political conventions
    - 1948 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 426)
    - 1948 Dec. (Film-reel 427)
    - 1949 Jan.-Feb. 9 (Film-reel 722)
      Part of Feb. 9
    - 1949 Feb.-June 22 (Film-reel 723)
      Rest of Feb. 9; May 18 missing; part of June 22, Pink String and Sealing Wax
    - 1949 June 22-Sept 28 (Film-reel 724)
      Rest of June 22, Pink String and Sealing Wax; part of Sept. 28 Climax'
    - 1949 Sept. 28-1950 Feb. 8 (Film-reel 725)
      Rest of Sept. 28 Climax; Feb. 8 to end of Act II
    - 1950 Feb. 8-June 14 (Film-reel 726)
      Feb. 8 Act III, The Dark Towers
    - 1950 June 21-Oct. 11 (Film-reel 729)
      Part of Oct. 11, The Great Broxopp
    - 1950 Oct. 11 (Film-reel 730)
      End of Oct. 11, The Great Broxopp
    - 1950 Oct. 11 (Film-reel 737)
      Pages 13-21 of Act II, The Great Broxopp
    - 1951 Jan.-Feb 28 (Film-reel 789)
    - 1951 Feb. 28-June 27 (Film-reel 790)
    - 1951 June 27-Nov. 7 (Film-reel 791)
    - 1951 Nov. 7-Dec. (Film-reel 792)
  - Matinee Theatre, 1958; 45
    - Comedy Time, 1958 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 1008)
    - Modern Romances, 1958 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 1008)
    - Tic-Tac-Dough, 1958 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 1008)
  - Other Programming, 1929-1955; 46
    - Alice Bailey's Desserts commercials, 1941 Mar.-Apr. (Film-reel 170)
    - Bing Crosby, 1945 Jan.-June (Film-reel 276)
    - Bing Crosby pictures and press notices, circa 1933 (Film-reel 343)
    - Bobby Benson Show, 1951 Jan. (Film-reel 792)
    - Commercials, 1942 Jan.-June (Film-reel 343)
    - Continuities, 1929-1930 (Film-reel 120)
    - Delicate Story, 1951 (Film-reel 974)
    - Edgar Bergen Show, 1954 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 991)
    - Edgar Bergen Show, 1955 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 992)
    - Edward Everett Hale, 1945 July-Sept. (Film-reel 276)
    - Frank Morgan, 1945 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 276)
    - International, 1949 Jan. (Film-reel 717)
    - Kraft Mayonnaise commercials, 1942 Jan.-June (Film-reel 343)
    - Kraft Miracle Whip article, 1933 (Film-reel 343)
    - Kraft Music Hall, 1946 (Film-reel 306)
      Missing Sept. 26
    - Kraft Music Hall, 1936 June (Film-reel 343)
    - Kraft Summer Show, 1949 Summer (Film-reel 722)
    - Kraft Summer show--Nelson Eddy, 1948 June-Sept. (Film-reel 424)
    - Kraft Television Theatre Side 1, 1954 Jan.-Feb. 25 (Film-reel 990)
      Act III of Feb. 25 broadcast
    - Kraft Television Theatre Side 1, 1954 July 8-Nov. 10 (Film-reel 991)
      Acts I-III of Nov. 10 broadcast
    - Kraft Television Theatre Side 2, 1954 Feb. 25-July 7 (Film-reel 990)
    - Kraft Television Theatre Side 2, 1954 Nov. 10-Dec. (Film-reel 991)
    - Parkay margarine--The Great Gildersleeve, 1941 Sept.-Oct. (Film-reel 343)
    - Show, 1945 (Film-reel 276)
      No broadcast Apr. 12
    - Speech by Gen. G.S. Patton Jr., 1942 Oct. 28 (Film-reel 343)
    - Spot announcements, 1948 July 16 (Film-reel 422)
      In Spanish for Puerto Rico and Venezuela
    - The Falcon, 1950 (Film-reel 730)
    - The Falcon, 1951 Jan.-Aug. 22 (Film-reel 792)
    - The Falcon, 1951 Aug. 22-30 (Film-reel 793)
    - Tom Corbett, Space Cadet, 1955 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 992)
- Lamont-Corliss, 1929-1942; 26
  - Danya, 1937-1942; 47
    - Commercials, 1940 Oct.-1941 Nov. (Film-reel 170)
    - Commercials, 1941 Dec.-1942 Apr. (Film-reel 244)
    - Commercials, testimonials, 1937-1939 (Film-reel 159)
    - Spot announcements, 1940 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 174)
  - Peter's Milk Cocoa, 1929; 48
    - 1929 (Film-reel 11)
- Lamont-Corliss (Pond's creams), 1930-1955; 27
  - Pond's Theatre TV, 1955; 49
    - Anna Christie, 1955 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Autumn Crocus, 1955 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Billy Budd, 1955 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Candle Light, 1955 May 5 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Coquette, 1955 July 7 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Cynara, 1955 May 12 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Death is a Spanish Dancer, 1955 June 20 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Erica, 1955 June 2 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Hang Up My Guns, 1955 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Joe Landry's Kid, 1955 Feb. 24 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Life and Taxes, 1955 June 9 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Mother is watching, 1955 June 16 (Film-reel 1000)
    - No Riders, 1955 Apr. 14 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Prologue to Glory, 1955 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Cornered Man, 1955 Jan. 27 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Dover Road, 1955 Feb. 17 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Fascinating Stranger, 1955 June 23 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Forger, 1955 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Glass Parlor, 1955 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Hickory Limb, 1955 Jan. 13 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Kingdom of Andrew Jones, 1955 May 26 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Rugged Mountains, 1955 Jan. 20 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Silver Box, 1955 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 1000)
    - The Ways of Courage, 1955 May 19 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Thirty, Honey, Thirty, 1955 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 1000)
    - Thunder Rock, 1955 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 1000)
  - Other Programming, 1930-1944; 50
    - Afternoon Tea, 1930 Dec. (Film-reel 244)
    - Commercials, 1938-1939 (Film-reel 30)
    - Commercials, 1930 Dec.-1931 Dec. (Film-reel 139)
    - Commercials, 1933 Jan.-July (Film-reel 158)
      Mrs. Roosevelt through Mar. 3
    - Commercials, 1933 Aug.-1934 Jan. (Film-reel 158)
    - Commercials, 1941 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 171)
    - Commercials, 1942 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 171)
    - Commercials--Maude Adams, 1934 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 158)
      Feb. 16 and 23 missing
    - Commercials--Mrs. Roosevelt, 1937 Apr.-July (Film-reel 158)
    - Husbands and Wives, 1936 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 158)
    - Husbands and Wives, 1937 (Film-reel 159)
    - Leo Reisman and Orchestra, 1932 (Film-reel 244)
    - Spot announcements, 1943 Jan.-Sept. (Film-reel 201)
    - Those We Love, 1938 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 28)
    - Those We Love, 1938 Feb.-1939 Feb. (Film-reel 29)
    - Those We Love, 1939 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 30)
    - 1943 July-1944 June (Film-reel 262)
- Lever Brothers, 1930-1957; 28
  - Life and Love of Dr. Susan, 1939; 51
    - 1939 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 134)
      In this order: production sheet, as-broadcast script, original JWT script before as-broadcast changes
    - 1939 Mar.-July (Film-reel 135)
    - 1939 July-Nov. (Film-reel 136)
    - 1939 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 137)
  - Lux Radio Theatre, 1934-1955; 52
    - Adam and Evalyn, 1952 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 911)
    - African Queen, 1952 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 912)
    - Audition script, 1936 Mar. 19-20 (Film-reel 104)
    - Aunt Jenny hitchhikes, 1949 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 730)
    - Branded, 1952 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 911)
    - Capt. Horatio Hornblower, 1952 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 911)
    - Come to the Stable, 1952 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 911)
    - Duchess of Idaho, 1952 Jan. 7 (Film-reel 911)
    - Five Fingers, 1952 Oct. 13 (Film-reel 912)
    - Follow the Sun, 1952 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 911)
    - Goodbye My Fancy, 1952 Jan. 14 (Film-reel 911)
    - Grounds for Marriage, 1952 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 912)
    - Here Comes the Groom, 1952 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 911)
    - Here Comes the Groom, 1952 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 912)
    - I Can Get It for You Wholesale, 1952 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 911)
    - I'll Never Forget You, 1952 Sept. 22 (Film-reel 911)
    - Kim, 1952 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 911)
    - King Solomon's Mines, 1952 Dec. 1 (Film-reel 912)
    - Les Miserables, 1952 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 912)
    - My Blue Heaven, 1952 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 911)
    - My Six Convicts, 1952 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 912)
    - My Son John, 1952 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 912)
    - No Highway in the Sky, 1952 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 911)
    - On Moonlight Bay, 1952 May 5 (Film-reel 911)
    - Recording script, 1936 Mar. 18 (Film-reel 104)
    - Riding High, 1952 May 12 (Film-reel 911)
    - Room for One More, 1952 May 26 (Film-reel 911)
    - Royal Wedding, 1952 Apr. 14 (Film-reel 911)
    - Showboat, 1952 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 911)
    - Side 1, 1954 Jan.-Oct. 26 (Film-reel 992)
      Act III of Oct. 26 broadcast
    - Side 2, 1954 Oct. 26-Dec. (Film-reel 992)
    - Strictly Dishonorable, 1952 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 912)
    - Submarine Command, 1952 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 912)
    - Take Care of My Little Girl, 1952 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 911)
    - The Blue Veil, 1952 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 912)
    - The Crisis, 1952 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 911)
    - The Magnificent Yankee, 1952 May 19 (Film-reel 911)
    - The Mating of Millie, 1949 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 730)
      Acts III
    - The Men Without a Country, 1934 Feb. 22 (Film-reel 343)
    - The Model and the Marriage Broker, 1952 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 912)
    - Top o' the Morning, 1952 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 911)
    - Two Weeks with Love, 1952 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 912)
    - Union Station, 1952 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 911)
    - Viva Zapata, 1952 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 912)
    - Westward the Women, 1952 Dec. 29 (Film-reel 912)
    - Young Man With a Horn, 1952 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 911)
    - 1934-1935 June (Film-reel 103)
    - 1935 June-Dec. (Film-reel 104)
    - 1936 Jan-Mar. (Film-reel 104)
    - 1936 Mar.-Nov. (Film-reel 105)
    - 1936 Nov.-1937 Sept. (Film-reel 106)
    - 1937 Oct.-1938 Apr. (Film-reel 107)
    - 1938 May-1939 Jan. (Film-reel 108)
    - 1939 Feb.-Nov. (Film-reel 109)
    - 1939 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 110)
    - 1938 Nov. (Film-reel 153)
    - 1940 Jan. (Film-reel 182)
    - 1940 Jan.-Oct. (Film-reel 183)
    - 1941 Oct.-July (Film-reel 184)
    - 1941 Sept.-1942 Apr. (Film-reel 185)
      No summer broadcasts; Act III of Lady Eve, Mar. 9 1942 missing due to President's talk
    - 1942 Apr.-Dec. (Film-reel 186)
    - 1943 Jan.-May (Film-reel 200)
    - 1943 May-July, Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 201)
      Nov. 8 broadcast missing
    - 1944 Jan.-July 3, Sept. (Film-reel 236)
    - 1944 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 237)
    - 1945 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 276)
    - 1945 Feb.-Dec. (Film-reel 276)
    - 1945 Dec. 17-31 (Film-reel 277)
    - 1946 Mar.-Dec. (Film-reel 307)
      No summer broadcasts
    - 1934 Nov. (Film-reel 343)
    - 1947 Jan.-June, Aug.-Sept. (Film-reel 367)
      Through second act of Sept. 15, The Seventh Veil
    - 1947 Sept. 15-Dec. (Film-reel 368)
      From third act of Sept. 15, The Seventh Veil
    - 1948 (Film-reel 416)
      No broadcast June 21
    - 1949 (Film-reel 731)
      End of Jan. 3 The Mating of Millie; Dec. 26 to end of Act I
    - 1949 Dec. 26-1950 Oct. 30 (Film-reel 732)
      End of Dec. 26; Oct. 30 to end of Act II
    - 1950 Oct. 30 (Film-reel 733)
      End of broadcast
    - 1951 Jan.-Nov. 12 (Film-reel 793)
    - 1951 Nov. 12-Dec. (Film-reel 794)
    - 1953 (Film-reel 987)
    - 1955 Jan.-June (Film-reel 1001)
  - Lux Video Theatre, 1950-1957; 53
    - A Child Is Born, 1952 Dec. 22 (Film-reel 913)
    - A Message For Janice, 1952 Sept. 29 (Film-reel 913)
    - Amo, Amas, Amat, 1952 Dec. 1 (Film-reel 913)
    - Ceylon Treasure, 1952 Jan. 14 (Film-reel 912)
    - Country Lawyer, 1952 Oct. 20 (Film-reel 913)
    - Decision, 1952 Apr. 14 (Film-reel 912)
    - Fear, 1952 Dec. 8 (Film-reel 913)
    - Ferry Crisis at Friday Point, 1952 May 19 (Film-reel 912)
    - For Goodness Sake, 1952 Jan. 28 (Film-reel 912)
    - Garveau '83, 1952 June 2 (Film-reel 912)
    - Gilia, 1952 June 16 (Film-reel 913)
    - Happily But Not Forever, 1952 Sept. 22 (Film-reel 913)
    - Hunt the Man Down, 1952 Apr. 7 (Film-reel 912)
    - I Can't Remember, 1952 June 30 (Film-reel 913)
      July 7 broadcast missing
    - Ile, 1952 Sept. 8 (Film-reel 913)
    - Julie, 1952 Mar. 24 (Film-reel 912)
    - Kelly, 1952 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 912)
    - Legacy of Love, 1952 Oct. 6 (Film-reel 913)
      Oct. 13 broadcast missing
    - Life, Liberty, and Orrin Dooley, 1952 Feb. 18 (Film-reel 912)
    - Marriage in the Beginning, 1952 May 12 (Film-reel 912)
    - Masquerade, 1952 May 5 (Film-reel 912)
    - Mr. Finchley Versus the Atom Bomb, 1952 Jan. 7 (Film-reel 912)
    - Night Be Quiet, 1952 Mar. 3 (Film-reel 912)
    - Operation Weekend, 1952 Apr. 21 (Film-reel 912)
    - Pattern for Glory, 1952 May 26 (Film-reel 912)
    - Salad Days, 1952 Apr. 28 (Film-reel 912)
    - Side 1, 1954 Sept.2-Dec. (Film-reel 992)
    - Something to Celebrate, 1952 Nov. 10 (Film-reel 913)
    - Son Wanted, 1952 July 14 (Film-reel 913)
    - Song for a Banjo, 1952 Dec. 15 (Film-reel 913)
    - Stone's Throw, 1952 Sept. 15 (Film-reel 913)
    - Taste, 1952 Mar. 31 (Film-reel 912)
    - The Bargain, 1952 Feb. 25 (Film-reel 912)
    - The Brigadier, 1952 July 21 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Face of Autumn, 1952 Nov. 3 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Foggy, Foggy Dew, 1952 Mar. 17 (Film-reel 912)
    - The Game of Chess, 1952 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 912)
    - The Hill, 1952 Nov. 24 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Key, 1952 Dec. 29 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Lesson, 1952 June 9 (Film-reel 912)
    - The Lesson, 1952 June 9 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Magnolia Touch, 1952 Aug. 25 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Man Who Struck It Rich, 1952 Nov. 17 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Orchard, 1952 Aug. 11 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Promotion, 1952 Mar. 10 (Film-reel 912)
    - The Return of Ulysses, 1952 Sept. 1 (Film-reel 913)
    - The Sound of Waves Breaking, 1952 Jan. 21 (Film-reel 912)
    - Three Hours Between Planes, 1952 Oct. 27 (Film-reel 913)
    - Two Make Four, 1952 Aug. 4 (Film-reel 913)
    - Two Pale Horsemen, 1952 July 28 (Film-reel 913)
    - Welcome Home Lefty, 1952 June 23 (Film-reel 913)
    - You Be the Bad Guy, 1952 Aug. 18 (Film-reel 913)
    - 1950 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 733)
    - 1951 Jan.-Sept. 10 (Film-reel 794)
    - 1951 Sept. 10-Dec. (Film-reel 795)
    - 1953 (Film-reel 987)
    - 1954 Jan.-June, Aug.-Sept 2 (Film-reel 991)
      Acts I-III of Sept. 2 broadcast
    - 1955 Aug. (Film-reel 992)
    - 1955 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 1000)
    - 1955 Jan.-July (Film-reel 1001)
    - 1955 Mar.-Apr. (Film-reel 1002)
    - 1956 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 1003)
    - 1956 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 1004)
    - 1956 Mar.-Aug. (Film-reel 1005)
    - 1957 Mar.-Aug. (Film-reel 1006)
  - Other Programming, 1930-1956; 54
    - Arthur Godfrey television, 1956 Jan.-Mar. (Film-reel 1003)
    - Auditions--Lux Soap Revue, 1930 (Film-reel 259)
    - Aunt Jenny hitchhikes, 1943 July-Aug. (Film-reel 201)
    - Aunt Jenny hitchhikes, 1944 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 236)
    - Aunt Jenny hitchhikes, 1948 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 416)
    - Commercials, 1939 (Film-reel 137)
    - Edgar Bergen & Charlie McCarthy--CBS Biography, 1949 Feb. 11 (Film-reel 368)
    - Lux Flakes spot announcements, 1941 Mar.-June; 1942 Feb. (Film-reel 186)
    - Lux Hour of Mystery and Romance, 1952 June (Film-reel 911)
    - Lux test commercials, 1943 June 23 (Film-reel 201)
    - Lux Toilet Soap Movie Club, 1938 (Film-reel 343)
      London Office; programs 41-59
    - Lux Toilet Soap spot announcements, 1941 Mar.-Dec.; 1942 Feb. (Film-reel 186)
    - Lux Toilet Soap spot announcements, 1942 Feb.-May (Film-reel 244)
    - Lux Toilet Soap--V.E. Meadows Beauty School no. 1-13, 1931 Aug.-Oct. (Film-reel 244)
    - The Clock scripts, 1949 Oct. (Film-reel 448)
    - The Clock scripts, 1949 Oct.-1950 Mar. (Film-reel 449)
    - The Family Man--Canada, 1939-1940 (Film-reel 35)
    - V.E. Meadows Beauty School, 1931 July 28 (Film-reel 259)
  - Peggy Winthrop, 1930-1931; 55
    - 1930-1931 Sept. (Film-reel 102)
    - 1931 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 103)
      Many broadcasts missing
    - 1931 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 244)
  - Vimms, 1944; 56
    - Bright Horizons--Frank Sinatra, 1944 Jan.-Oct. (Film-reel 278)
    - Commercials, 1944 July (Film-reel 215)
    - Deal Hitch-Hikes, 1944 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 278)
    - Deal live copy, 1944 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 278)
    - Deal spots, 1944 Feb.-Mar. (Film-reel 278)
    - Frank Sinatra Program, 1944 Jan.-June; Aug-Dec. (Film-reel 237)
      Missing Sept. 20, Oct. 4 broadcasts
    - Hitch Hike--Bright Horizons, 1944 Jan. 3 (Film-reel 237)
    - 1944 Mar. (Film-reel 262)
- Libby McNeil & Libby, 1929-1950; 29
  - Monitor Reports, 1946-1950; 57
    - 1946 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 356)
    - 1949 (Film-reel 530)
    - 1950 (Film-reel 530)
  - Mr. Christoph's comments on synopsis, 1949-1950; 58
    - 1949 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 529)
    - 1949 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 530)
    - 1950 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 530)
  - My True Story, 1945-1950; 59
    - Commercials, 1945 (Film-reel 445)
    - Commercials, 1945 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 446)
    - Commercials, 1946 May (Film-reel 446)
    - Magazine outlines, 1949-1950 (Film-reel 531)
    - Monitor Reports, 1945 (Film-reel 445)
    - Monitor Reports, 1946 (Film-reel 446)
    - Scripts, 1950 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 530)
    - 1947 (Film-reel 354)
      Starts with episode 708
    - 1947 June-Oct. (Film-reel 355)
      Starts with episode 823
    - 1947 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 356)
      Starts with episode 918
    - 1946 Apr.-Aug., Oct. (Film-reel 357)
      Starts with episode 513
    - 1946 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 358)
      Starts with episode 608
    - 1946 Aug. 14-15 (Film-reel 360)
    - 1945 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 446)
    - 1947 Dec.-1948 Mar. (Film-reel 446)
    - 1948 Mar.-Aug. (Film-reel 447)
    - 1948 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 448)
    - 1949 Jan.-Feb. (Film-reel 449)
    - 1949 Mar.-Aug. (Film-reel 528)
    - 1949 Aug.-Dec. (Film-reel 529)
  - Other Programming, 1929-1948; 60
    - Around the World with Libby, 1929 June-1930 June (Film-reel 155)
    - Commercials, 1948 (Film-reel 418)
    - Ray Perkins, 1930 Oct.-1931 Mar. (Film-reel 155)
    - Ray Perkins, 1931 Apr.-Dec. (Film-reel 156)
    - The Libby Adventure Hour, 1934 Oct. 1 (Film-reel 243)
    - The Libby Grocer, 1930 Sept.-Dec. (Film-reel 155)
- Lorillard (Old Gold Cigarettes), 1940-1944; 30
  - Auditions, 1941; 61
    - Benny Goodman, undated (Film-reel 188)
    - Crossroads USA, 1941 Feb. 4 (Film-reel 188)
    - Girls Trio, 1941 Feb. 3 (Film-reel 188)
  - Brooklyn baseball, 1943-1944; 62
    - Play by play, 1943 Apr.-July (Film-reel 212)
      Brigg's Pipe Mixture also mentioned
    - Play by play, 1943 July-Oct.; 1944 Mar.-Aug. (Film-reel 213)
    - 1944 Aug.-Oct. (Film-reel 214)
  - Commercials, 1941-1944; 63
    - WGN Bob Elson, 1941 Jan.-Aug. (Film-reel 189)
      Muriel, Van Bibber cigars, Friends pipe tobacco also mentioned in scripts
    - 1941 Feb. 10 (Film-reel 188)
    - 1942 Apr.-Dec. (Film-reel 189)
    - 1943 Jan. (Film-reel 192)
    - 1942 Dec.-1943 Jan. (Film-reel 211)
    - 1943 Dec.-1944 June (Film-reel 211)
    - 1944 Oct.-Nov. (Film-reel 212)
  - Herbert Marshall, 1941-1942; 64
    - 1941 Nov.-Dec. (Film-reel 187)
    - 1942 Jan.-Apr. (Film-reel 209)
    - 1942 Apr. 24 (Film-reel 343)
  - N.Y. Giants football, 1943-1944; 65
    - Play by play, 1943 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 212)
    - 1943 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 210)
    - 1944 Oct.-Dec. (Film-reel 214)
  - New York, 1940-1941; 66
    - WABC, 1941 Mar. (Film-reel 188)
    - WEAF, 1941 Mar. 19 (Film-reel 188)
    - WEAF A-M, 1941 June 30 (Film-reel 188)
    - WHN, 1940 Dec.-1941 Oct. (Film-reel 188)
    - WHN, 1941 (Film-reel 188)
    - WQXR, 1941 Jan.; July 1941 (Film-reel 188)
  - Other Programming, 1940-1944; 67
    - 1943 World Series (Film-reel 215)
    - Allan Jones, Frankie Carle, etc., 1944 Apr.-Oct. (Film-reel 215)
    - Andy Russell, Les Tremayne, etc., 1944 July (Film-reel 214)
    - Andy Russell, Les Tremayne, etc., 1944 Aug.-Oct. (Film-reel 215)
      Edgar Bergen guest on Aug. 13
    - Benny Goodman, What's New?, 1941 Feb.-May (Film-reel 187)
    - Benny Goodman--New program announcement, 1941 Feb. 6 (Film-reel 188)
    - Bob Crosby and program, 1943 July-Dec. (Film-reel 210)
    - Bob Crosby, Les Tremayne, 1944 Jan.-June (Film-reel 214)
    - Broadcast, 1943 Mar. 8 (Film-reel 211)
    - Campus News, 1942 Oct.-1943 Jan. (Film-reel 210)